<resources>
    <string name="app_name">StackViewPager</string>

    <string name="sample_data">A 2012 study by the Asian Development Bank and the Comparative Education Research Centre at the University of Hong Kong pointed out that private tutoring can dominate the lives of young people and their families, maintain and exacerbate social inequalities, divert needed household income into an unregulated industry, and create inefficiencies in education systems. It can also undermine official statements about fee-free education and create threats to social cohesion.[2]  In South Korea, nearly 90% of elementary students receive some sort of shadow education.[3] In Hong Kong, about 85% of senior secondary students do so.[4] 60% of primary students in West Bengal, India,[5] and 60% of secondary students in Kazakhstan receive private tutoring.[6]  Demand for tutoring in Asia is exploding; by comparison globally, shadow education is most extensive in Asia. This is partly due to the stratification of education systems, cultural factors, perceptions of shortcomings in regular school systems, and the combination of growing wealth and smaller family sizes.[2] Therefore, the education sector has become a profitable industry which businesses have created different kinds of products and advertisement such us \"the king/queen of tutorial\", a usual advertisement tactic of Hong Kong tutorial centers that has spread to South Korea, Thailand, Sri Lanka and India where tutors achieve \"celebrity-like status\".[7] In some cases, successful Southeast Asian tutors will even embrace the title of \"tutor\". Online private tutor matching platform and online learning platform offering online learning materials are other creations.  In Cambodia, most tutoring is provided by teachers,[8] whereas in Hong Kong, it is provided by individuals, small companies or large companies.[9] In Mongolia, most tutoring is labor-intensive,[10] while entrepreneurs in South Korea make use of computers and other forms of technology.[2]  Policy</string>

</resources>
